Along the ancient path of the Monongahela River,
على طول الطريق القديم المحاذي لنهر مونونجاهيلا،
Braddock, Pennsylvania sits in the eastern region of Allegheny County,
برادوك، من ولاية بنسلفانيا في المنطقة الشرقية من مقاطعة ألغينيي،
approximately nine miles outside of Pittsburgh.
خارج بيتسبرغ بحوالي 9 أميال.
An industrial suburb,
تعتبر برادوك الضاحية الصناعية
Braddock is home to Andrew Carnegie's first steel mill,
وهي موطن أول مصنع للفولاذ لأندرو كارنيجي،
the Edgar Thomson Works.
مصانع إدغار طومسن.
Operating since 1875,
المصنع الذي يعمل منذ عام 1875،
it is the last functioning steel mill in the region.
يعتبر آخر مصنع فولاذ قائم في المنطقة.
For 12 years, I have produced collaborative portraits,
لمدة 12 عامًا، قمت بإنتاج صور تعاونية،
still lifes, landscapes and aerial views
وصور لمناظر طبيعية وأخرى من منظور جوي
in order to build a visual archive to address the intersection
وذلك بهدف بناء أرشيف بصري لإبراز الترابط
of the steel industry,
بين صناعة الفولاذ
the environment,
والبيئة
and the health care system's impact on the bodies of my family and community.
وتأثير نظم الرعاية الصحية على صحة عائلتي والمجتمع.
The tradition and grand narrative of Braddock
تتكون معظم الحكايات المهمة والتقليدية في برادوك
is mostly comprised of stories of industrialists and trade unions.
من قصص عن أرباب الصناعة ونقابات العمال.
Currently, the new narrative about Braddock,
أما الآن، فالقصص المنتشرة عن برادوك
a poster child for Rust Belt revitalization,
فهي نموذج من إحياء حزام الصدأ
is a story of urban pioneers discovering a new frontier.
وهي قصص لرواد المناطق الحضرية المكتشفين لحدود الجديدة.
Mass media has omitted the fact that Braddock is predominantly black.
تناست وسائل الإعلام حقيقة أن برادوك أغلب سكانها من السود.
Our existence has been co-opted, silenced and erased.
أصبح وجودنا موضوع اختيار واسكات ومحو.
Fourth generation in a lineage of women,
أعتبر الجيل الرابع في النسب من النساء
I was raised under the protection and care of Grandma Ruby,
لقد كبرت في رعاية وحماية جدتي روبي
off 8th Street at 805 Washington Avenue.
قبالة شارع رقم 8 في 805 شارع واشنطن.
She worked as a manager for Goodwill.
وعملت كمدير لشركة "النوايا الحسنة".
Mom was a nurse's aid.
أما أمي فقد كانت مساعدة ممرضة.
She watched the steel mills close and white flight to suburban developments.
راقبت عن قرب مصانع الفولاذ وهجرة البيض نحو الضواحي لتطويرها،
By the time my generation walked the streets,
ومع خروجنا جيلنا للشوارع ،
disinvestment at the local, state and federal level,
سحب الاستثمار على المستوى المحلي والدولي والفدرالي،
eroded infrastructure,
والبنية التحتية المتآكلة،
and the War on Drugs dismantled my family and community.
والحرب ضد المخدرات قامت بتفكيك أسرتي والمجتمع.
Grandma Ruby's stepfather Gramps
كان زوج جدتي جرامبس
was one of few black men to retire from Carnegie's mill with his pension.
واحدا من السود القلة الذين تقاعدوا من مصنع كارنيجي وحصل على راتب التقاعد.
He worked in high temperatures,
كان يعمل تحت درجات حرارة عالية،
tearing down and rebuilding furnaces, cleaning up spilt metal and slag.
يقوم بهدم الأفران وإعادة بناءها وتنظيف ما تناثر من حديد وبقايا الصهر .
The history of a place is written on the body and the landscape.
نُقش تاريخ هذا المكان على الأجساد و على المناظر الطبيعية ،
Areas of heavy truck traffic,
الممرات التي تمر منها الشاحنات الثقيلة،
exposure to benzene and atomized metals,
تتعرض لمادة البنزين ورذاذ المعادن ،
risk cancer and lupus.
وخطر الإصابة بالسرطان وداء الذئبة الجلدي .
One hundred twenty-three licensed beds, 652 employees,
123 سريراً مرخصاً، 652 موظفاً،
rehabilitation programs decimated.
قااموا بإيقاف برامج إعادة التأهيل.
A housing discrimination lawsuit against Allegheny County
وقاموا برفع قضية التمييز في مجال الإسكان ضد مقاطعة ألغاني
removed where the projects Talbot Towers once stood.
وتمت إزالة المشاريع حيث كانت أبراج تالبوت منتصبة ذات مرة
Recent rezoning for more light industry has since appeared.
وقع مؤخرا إعادة تقسيم المنطقة لمزيد من الصناعات الخفيفة التي ظهرت في ذلك الوقت.
Google Maps and Google Earth pixelations conceal the flammable waste
وتم إخفاء أثر النفايات القابلة للاشتعال في خرائط جوجل و جوجل ارث باعتماد البيكسل
being used to squeeze the Bunn family off their home and land.
الذي اُعتمد كوسيلة لطرد عائلة بون من منزلهم وأرضهم .
In 2013, I chartered a helicopter
في عام 2013، استأجرت طائرة هيلكوبتر
with my cameras to document this aggressive dispossession.
ومعي الكاميرا لتوثيق السلب العدواني للملكية
In flight, my observation reveals thousands of plastic white bundles
أثناء التحليق، لاحظت الالاف من أكوام البلاستيك االبيضاء
owned by a conservation industry
التابعة للصناعة الحافظة
that claims it's eco-friendly
والتي تدّعي أنها صديقة للبيئة
and recycles millions of tires
وتقوم بإعادة تصنيع الملايين من الإطارات
to preserve people's lives
بهدف الحفاظ على حياة الناس
and to improve people's lives.
وتحسين حياتهم.
My work spirals from the micro to the macro level,
تصاعدت وتيرة وشهرة أعمالي لتصبح مشهورة
excavating hidden histories.
وكشفت النقاب عن التاريخ المكتوم.
Recently, at the Seattle Art Museum,
مؤخرا، في متحف سياتل للفن،
Isaac Bunn and I mounted this exhibition,
قمنا ، أنا واسحاق بون باستغلال المعرض المقام به،
and the exhibition was used as a platform to launch his voice.
واستعملناه كمنصة لايصال صوته،
Through reclamation of our narrative,
من خلال تصحيح رواياتنا،
we will continue to fight historic erasure and socioeconomic inequality.
سنستمر في محاربة المحو التاريخي وعدم المساواة الاجتماعية والاقتصادية.
Thank you.
شكرًا لكم.
(Applause)
(تصفيق)